Contact

dvnurse76@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/denise-vermaat-5a9a78a8 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management Microsoft Word Leadership

Denise Vermaat

Clinical Specialist/Nurse Leader
Boca Raton

Summary

My goal is to obtain as a Leader in Nursing Education. I possess over 20 years of pediatric and adult nursing in several specialty fields including pediatric cardiac intensive care, adult intensive care, pediatric intensive care, oncology, NICU, ER, and general pediatrics. I also possess several years of leadership experience including assistant nurse manager and charge nurse, as well as a Nurse Educator and Clinical Specialist.

With my experience and with my studies I can be an excellent leader and innovative educator. I want to drive nurses to reach and exceed their potentials. I believe in positive reinforcement and transformational leadership, involving all nurses to come together for a positive, uplifting, and exceptional working environment. This will in turn transform itself into to care we provide for our patients. I want employees to feel valued and I expect them to participate in the growth of the working environment. I look to maintain staff and help them to reach their fullest potentials. Nursing is not just a job, but a dedicated career. I want to help promote healthy lifestyles for children, adults, and their caregivers.

Experience

Broward Health Medical Center
Pediatric Clinical Specialist/ Nurse Educator
August 2013 - Present (7 years 1 month)

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Responsible for orientation, education, and professional development of 70+ pediatric and pediatric Hematology/Oncology nurses in a leading Pediatric Hospital in South Florida

Palms West Hospital
Registered Nurse
November 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

Registered Nurse on a pediatric hematology/oncology unit.

Joe DiMaggio Children's Hospital Registered Nurse January 2014 - August 2014 (8 months)

Registered Nurse in a Pediatric Cardiac Intensive Care Unit

West Boca Medical Center
Registered Nurse- trained as charge nurse
August 2013 - December 2013 (5 months)

Registered Nurse on a busy pediatric unit, cross trained to NICU and PICU.

St. Christopher's Hospital for Children Registered Nurse- frequently charge nurse May 2007 - August 2013 (6 years 4 months) Greater Philadelphia Area

Registered nurse in an urban pediatric hospital. Worked in pediatric medical/ surgical units, Cardiac Intensive Care Unit, Pediatric Hematology/Oncology, cross trained to Emergency Room, Neonatal Intensive Care, Step Down Special Care Unit. Frequently functioned as charge nurse.

Underwood Memorial Hospital Registered Nurse- pediatrics and NICU November 2006 - March 2008 (1 year 5 months)

Voorhees Pediatric Home Care Assistant nurse manager September 2005 - September 2007 (2 years 1 month)

Al DuPont Hospital for Children RN- occasional charge nurse November 1998 - January 2005 (6 years 3 months)

Education

Drexel University

MSN in Nursing Leadership and Management, Nursing Leadership and Management \cdot (2008 - 2016)

Drexel University

MSN, Healthcare Leadership & Management · (2008 - 2014)

Widener University

Bachelor of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1994 - 1998)

Pennsauken High School